{
  "logoUrl": "/logo-sensus.svg",
  "titleImgUrl": "/logo-giulietta.svg",
  "arrowImgUrl": "/Arrow.svg",
  "backgroundImage": "/circle.svg",
  "backgroundColor": "#70708c",
  "scrollColor": "",
  "steps": {
    "en": [
      {
        "code": "SKIN_UNDERTONE",
        "question": "What is your skin undertone?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "PINKISH - BEIGE - OLIVE",
            "logo": "Pelle_Beige_q1.svg",
            "value": "COOL"
          },
          {
            "answer": "PEACH - AMBER - IVORY",
            "logo": "Pelle_Pesca_q1.svg",
            "value": "WARM"
          }
        ],
        "next": "CONTINUE",
        "previous": "BACK"
      },
      {
        "code": "LIP_COLOR",
        "question": "What is the color of your lips?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "PINKISH",
            "logo": "Labbra_Rosate_q2.webp",
            "value": "COOL"
          },
          {
            "answer": "PEACH",
            "logo": "Labbra_Pesca_q2.webp",
            "value": "WARM"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "TANNED_SKIN",
        "question": "What is your skin color after tanning?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "TENDS TO REDDEN",
            "logo": "Pelle_Arrossata_q3.webp",
            "value": "COOL"
          },
          {
            "answer": "GOLDEN",
            "logo": "Pelle_Dorata_q3.webp",
            "value": "WARM"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "NATURAL_HAIR_COLOR",
        "question": "What is your natural hair color?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE_HORIZONTAL",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "DARK (levels 1 to 5)",
            "logo": "Hair_L5_q4.webp",
            "value": "DARK"
          },
          {
            "answer": "MEDIUM (levels 6 to 7)",
            "logo": "Hair_L7_q4.webp",
            "value": "MEDIUM"
          },
          {
            "answer": "LIGHT (levels 8 to 11)",
            "logo": "Hair_L9_q4.webp",
            "value": "LIGHT"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "EYEBROW_COLOR",
        "question": "What is the color of your eyebrows?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE_HORIZONTAL",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "DARK (levels 1 to 5)",
            "logo": "Hair_L5_q4.webp",
            "value": "DARK"
          },
          {
            "answer": "MEDIUM (levels 6 to 7)",
            "logo": "Hair_L7_q4.webp",
            "value": "MEDIUM"
          },
          {
            "answer": "LIGHT (levels 8 to 11)",
            "logo": "Hair_L9_q4.webp",
            "value": "LIGHT"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "PERSONALITY",
        "question": [
          "What is your",
          "personality like?"
        ],
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE_VERTICAL",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "SHY, RESERVED",
            "logo": "",
            "value": "INTROVERT"
          },
          {
            "answer": "EXUBERANT, OUTGOING",
            "logo": "",
            "value": "EXTROVERT"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "STEP_7",
        "question": "You're almost done",
        "type": "FORM_CONTACT",
        "last": "JUST ONE MORE STEP",
        "message": "Enter your email and discover the result",
        "placeholder": "Your email address",
        "send": "SEND",
        "consent1": {
          "text": [
            "Having read and understood the privacy policy",
            "I consent (by ticking the appropriate box) to the processing for the",
            "purposes indicated in point 2 letter A of the information (in summary: to respond to the request)"
          ]
        },
        "consent2": {
          "text": [
            "I consent (by ticking the appropriate box) to the processing for the",
            "purposes indicated in point 2 letter A of the information",
            "(in summary: receiving advertising/informational communications)"
          ]
        },
        "options": {
          "accept": "I Consent",
          "not_accept": "I Do Not Consent"
        }
      },
      {
        "code": "STEP_8",
        "question": "Thank you!",
        "type": "FINAL",
        "last": "YOU'RE DONE!",
        "email_check": {
          "text": [
            "Check your",
            "email inbox"
          ]
        },
        "store_locator": "VISIT OUR STORE LOCATOR"
      }
    ],
    "it": [
      {
        "code": "SKIN_UNDERTONE",
        "question": "Qual è il sottotono della tua pelle?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "ROSATO - BEIGE - OLIVASTRO",
            "logo": "Pelle_Beige_q1.svg",
            "value": "FREDDO"
          },
          {
            "answer": "PESCA - AVORIO - AMBRATO",
            "logo": "Pelle_Pesca_q1.svg",
            "value": "CALDO"
          }
        ],
        "next": "CONTINUA",
        "previous": "INDIETRO"
      },
      {
        "code": "LIP_COLOR",
        "question": "Qual è il colore della tue labbra?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "ROSATE",
            "logo": "Labbra_Rosate_q2.webp",
            "value": "FREDDO"
          },
          {
            "answer": "PESCA",
            "logo": "Labbra_Pesca_q2.webp",
            "value": "CALDO"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "TANNED_SKIN",
        "question": "Qual è il colore della tua pelle dopo l'abbronzatura?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "TENDENZA ARROSAMENTO",
            "logo": "Pelle_Arrossata_q3.webp",
            "value": "FREDDO"
          },
          {
            "answer": "DORATA",
            "logo": "Pelle_Dorata_q3.webp",
            "value": "CALDO"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "NATURAL_HAIR_COLOR",
        "question": "Qual è il colore naturale dei tuoi capelli?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE_HORIZONTAL",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "SCURI (livelli da 1 a 5)",
            "logo": "Hair_L5_q4.webp",
            "value": "SCURO"
          },
          {
            "answer": "MEDI (livelli da 6 a 7)",
            "logo": "Hair_L7_q4.webp",
            "value": "MEDIO"
          },
          {
            "answer": "CHIARI (livelli da 8 a 11)",
            "logo": "Hair_L9_q4.webp",
            "value": "CHIARO"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "EYEBROW_COLOR",
        "question": "Qual è il colore delle tue soppracciglia?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE_HORIZONTAL",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "SCURI (livelli da 1 a 5)",
            "logo": "Hair_L5_q4.webp",
            "value": "SCURO"
          },
          {
            "answer": "MEDI (livelli da 6 a 7)",
            "logo": "Hair_L7_q4.webp",
            "value": "MEDIO"
          },
          {
            "answer": "CHIARI (livelli da 8 a 11)",
            "logo": "Hair_L9_q4.webp",
            "value": "CHIARO"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "PERSONALITY",
        "question": [
          "Com'è il tuo",
          "carattere?"
        ],
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE_VERTICAL",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "TIMIDO, RISERVATO",
            "logo": "",
            "value": "INTROVERSO"
          },
          {
            "answer": "ESUBERANTE, ESTROVERSO",
            "logo": "",
            "value": "ESTROVERSO"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "STEP_7",
        "question": "Hai quasi finito",
        "type": "FORM_CONTACT",
        "last": "MANCA UN ULTIMO PASSO",
        "message": "Inserisci la tua mail e scopri il risultato",
        "placeholder": "Il tuo indirizzo mail",
        "send": "INVIA",
        "consent1": {
          "text": [
            "Preso atto dell'informativa e avendola compresa",
            "Acconsento (barrando l'apposita casella) al trattamento per le",
            "finalità indicate al punto 2 lett. A della informativa (in sintesi: per rispondere alla richiesta)"
          ]
        },
        "consent2": {
          "text": [
            "Acconsento (barrando l'apposita casella) al trattamento per le",
            "finalità indicate al punto 2 lett. A della informativa",
            "(in sintesi: ricezione di comunicazioni pubblicitarie/informative)"
          ]
        },
        "options": {
          "accept": "Acconsento",
          "not_accept": "Non Acconsento"
        }
      },
      {
        "code": "STEP_8",
        "question": "Grazie!",
        "type": "FINAL",
        "last": "HAI FINITO!",
        "email_check": {
          "text": [
            "Controlla la tua casella di",
            "posta elettronica"
          ]
        },
        "store_locator": "VISITA IL NOSTRO STORE LOCATOR"
      }
    ],
    "es": [
      {
        "code": "SKIN_UNDERTONE",
        "question": "¿Cuál es tu tono de piel?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "ROSADO - BEIGE - OLIVA",
            "logo": "Pelle_Beige_q1.svg",
            "value": "FRÍO"
          },
          {
            "answer": "MELOCOTÓN - ÁMBAR - MARFIL",
            "logo": "Pelle_Pesca_q1.svg",
            "value": "CÁLIDO"
          }
        ],
        "next": "CONTINUAR",
        "previous": "ATRÁS"
      },
      {
        "code": "LIP_COLOR",
        "question": "¿De qué color son tus labios?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "ROSADO",
            "logo": "Labbra_Rosate_q2.webp",
            "value": "FRÍO"
          },
          {
            "answer": "MELOCOTÓN",
            "logo": "Labbra_Pesca_q2.webp",
            "value": "CÁLIDO"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "TANNED_SKIN",
        "question": "¿Cómo es tu piel después de broncearte?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "TIENDE A ENROJECERSE",
            "logo": "Pelle_Arrossata_q3.webp",
            "value": "FRÍO"
          },
          {
            "answer": "DORADA",
            "logo": "Pelle_Dorata_q3.webp",
            "value": "CÁLIDO"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "NATURAL_HAIR_COLOR",
        "question": "¿Cuál es tu color natural de cabello?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE_HORIZONTAL",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "OSCURO (niveles 1 a 5)",
            "logo": "Hair_L5_q4.webp",
            "value": "OSCURO"
          },
          {
            "answer": "MEDIO (niveles 6 a 7)",
            "logo": "Hair_L7_q4.webp",
            "value": "MEDIO"
          },
          {
            "answer": "CLARO (niveles 8 a 11)",
            "logo": "Hair_L9_q4.webp",
            "value": "CLARO"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "EYEBROW_COLOR",
        "question": "¿De qué color son tus cejas?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE_HORIZONTAL",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "OSCURO (niveles 1 a 5)",
            "logo": "Hair_L5_q4.webp",
            "value": "OSCURO"
          },
          {
            "answer": "MEDIO (niveles 6 a 7)",
            "logo": "Hair_L7_q4.webp",
            "value": "MEDIO"
          },
          {
            "answer": "CLARO (niveles 8 a 11)",
            "logo": "Hair_L9_q4.webp",
            "value": "CLARO"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "PERSONALITY",
        "question": [
          "¿Cómo es tu",
          "personalidad?"
        ],
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE_VERTICAL",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "TÍMIDO, RESERVADO",
            "logo": "",
            "value": "INTROVERTIDO"
          },
          {
            "answer": "EXUBERANTE, EXTROVERTIDO",
            "logo": "",
            "value": "EXTROVERTIDO"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "STEP_7",
        "question": "Estás casi listo",
        "type": "FORM_CONTACT",
        "last": "SOLO UN PASO MÁS",
        "message": "Introduce tu correo y descubre el resultado",
        "placeholder": "Tu dirección de correo electrónico",
        "send": "ENVIAR",
        "consent1": {
          "text": [
            "He leído y comprendido la política de privacidad",
            "Doy mi consentimiento (marcando la casilla correspondiente) para el tratamiento con los",
            "fines indicados en el punto 2, letra A de la información (en resumen: responder a la solicitud)"
          ]
        },
        "consent2": {
          "text": [
            "Doy mi consentimiento (marcando la casilla correspondiente) para el tratamiento con los",
            "fines indicados en el punto 2, letra A de la información",
            "(en resumen: recibir comunicaciones publicitarias/informativas)"
          ]
        },
        "options": {
          "accept": "Doy mi consentimiento",
          "not_accept": "No doy mi consentimiento"
        }
      },
      {
        "code": "STEP_8",
        "question": "¡Gracias!",
        "type": "FINAL",
        "last": "¡HAS TERMINADO!",
        "email_check": {
          "text": [
            "Revisa tu",
            "bandeja de entrada"
          ]
        },
        "store_locator": "VISITA NUESTRO LOCALIZADOR DE TIENDAS"
      }
    ],
    "fr": [
      {
        "code": "SKIN_UNDERTONE",
        "question": "Quel est votre sous-ton de peau ?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "ROSE - BEIGE - OLIVE",
            "logo": "Pelle_Beige_q1.svg",
            "value": "FROID"
          },
          {
            "answer": "PÊCHE - AMBRE - IVOIRE",
            "logo": "Pelle_Pesca_q1.svg",
            "value": "CHAUD"
          }
        ],
        "next": "CONTINUER",
        "previous": "RETOUR"
      },
      {
        "code": "LIP_COLOR",
        "question": "Quelle est la couleur de vos lèvres ?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "ROSE",
            "logo": "Labbra_Rosate_q2.webp",
            "value": "FROID"
          },
          {
            "answer": "PÊCHE",
            "logo": "Labbra_Pesca_q2.webp",
            "value": "CHAUD"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "TANNED_SKIN",
        "question": "Quelle est la couleur de votre peau après un bronzage ?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "TEND À ROUGIR",
            "logo": "Pelle_Arrossata_q3.webp",
            "value": "FROID"
          },
          {
            "answer": "DORÉE",
            "logo": "Pelle_Dorata_q3.webp",
            "value": "CHAUD"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "NATURAL_HAIR_COLOR",
        "question": "Quelle est votre couleur naturelle de cheveux ?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE_HORIZONTAL",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "FONCÉ (niveaux 1 à 5)",
            "logo": "Hair_L5_q4.webp",
            "value": "FONCÉ"
          },
          {
            "answer": "MOYEN (niveaux 6 à 7)",
            "logo": "Hair_L7_q4.webp",
            "value": "MOYEN"
          },
          {
            "answer": "CLAIR (niveaux 8 à 11)",
            "logo": "Hair_L9_q4.webp",
            "value": "CLAIR"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "EYEBROW_COLOR",
        "question": "Quelle est la couleur de vos sourcils ?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE_HORIZONTAL",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "FONCÉ (niveaux 1 à 5)",
            "logo": "Hair_L5_q4.webp",
            "value": "FONCÉ"
          },
          {
            "answer": "MOYEN (niveaux 6 à 7)",
            "logo": "Hair_L7_q4.webp",
            "value": "MOYEN"
          },
          {
            "answer": "CLAIR (niveaux 8 à 11)",
            "logo": "Hair_L9_q4.webp",
            "value": "CLAIR"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "PERSONALITY",
        "question": [
          "Quelle est votre",
          "personnalité ?"
        ],
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE_VERTICAL",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "TIMIDE, RÉSERVÉ",
            "logo": "",
            "value": "INTROVERTI"
          },
          {
            "answer": "EXUBÉRANT, SOCIABLE",
            "logo": "",
            "value": "EXTRAVERTI"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "STEP_7",
        "question": "Vous y êtes presque",
        "type": "FORM_CONTACT",
        "last": "PLUS QU'UNE ÉTAPE",
        "message": "Entrez votre e-mail pour découvrir le résultat",
        "placeholder": "Votre adresse e-mail",
        "send": "ENVOYER",
        "consent1": {
          "text": [
            "Après avoir lu et compris la politique de confidentialité",
            "je consens (en cochant la case correspondante) au traitement des données",
            "pour les finalités indiquées au point 2 lettre A de l'information (en résumé : répondre à la demande)"
          ]
        },
        "consent2": {
          "text": [
            "Je consens (en cochant la case correspondante) au traitement des données",
            "pour les finalités indiquées au point 2 lettre A de l'information",
            "(en résumé : recevoir des communications publicitaires/informatives)"
          ]
        },
        "options": {
          "accept": "Je consens",
          "not_accept": "Je ne consens pas"
        }
      },
      {
        "code": "STEP_8",
        "question": "Merci !",
        "type": "FINAL",
        "last": "C'EST TERMINÉ !",
        "email_check": {
          "text": [
            "Vérifiez votre",
            "boîte de réception"
          ]
        },
        "store_locator": "VISITEZ NOTRE LOCALISATEUR DE MAGASINS"
      }
    ],
    "pt": [
      {
        "code": "SKIN_UNDERTONE",
        "question": "Qual é o seu subtom de pele?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "ROSA - BEGE - OLIVA",
            "logo": "Pelle_Beige_q1.svg",
            "value": "FRIO"
          },
          {
            "answer": "PÊSSEGO - ÂMBAR - MARFIM",
            "logo": "Pelle_Pesca_q1.svg",
            "value": "QUENTE"
          }
        ],
        "next": "CONTINUAR",
        "previous": "VOLTAR"
      },
      {
        "code": "LIP_COLOR",
        "question": "Qual é a cor dos seus lábios?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "ROSA",
            "logo": "Labbra_Rosate_q2.webp",
            "value": "FRIO"
          },
          {
            "answer": "PÊSSEGO",
            "logo": "Labbra_Pesca_q2.webp",
            "value": "QUENTE"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "TANNED_SKIN",
        "question": "Qual é a cor da sua pele depois do bronzeado?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "TENDE A FICAR VERMELHA",
            "logo": "Pelle_Arrossata_q3.webp",
            "value": "FRIO"
          },
          {
            "answer": "DOURADA",
            "logo": "Pelle_Dorata_q3.webp",
            "value": "QUENTE"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "NATURAL_HAIR_COLOR",
        "question": "Qual é a cor natural do seu cabelo?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE_HORIZONTAL",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "ESCURO (níveis 1 a 5)",
            "logo": "Hair_L5_q4.webp",
            "value": "ESCURO"
          },
          {
            "answer": "MÉDIO (níveis 6 a 7)",
            "logo": "Hair_L7_q4.webp",
            "value": "MÉDIO"
          },
          {
            "answer": "CLARO (níveis 8 a 11)",
            "logo": "Hair_L9_q4.webp",
            "value": "CLARO"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "EYEBROW_COLOR",
        "question": "Qual é a cor das suas sobrancelhas?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE_HORIZONTAL",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "ESCURO (níveis 1 a 5)",
            "logo": "Hair_L5_q4.webp",
            "value": "ESCURO"
          },
          {
            "answer": "MÉDIO (níveis 6 a 7)",
            "logo": "Hair_L7_q4.webp",
            "value": "MÉDIO"
          },
          {
            "answer": "CLARO (níveis 8 a 11)",
            "logo": "Hair_L9_q4.webp",
            "value": "CLARO"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "PERSONALITY",
        "question": [
          "Como é a sua",
          "personalidade?"
        ],
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE_VERTICAL",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "TÍMIDO, RESERVADO",
            "logo": "",
            "value": "INTROVERTIDO"
          },
          {
            "answer": "EXUBERANTE, SOCIÁVEL",
            "logo": "",
            "value": "EXTROVERTIDO"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "STEP_7",
        "question": "Você está quase lá",
        "type": "FORM_CONTACT",
        "last": "SÓ MAIS UM PASSO",
        "message": "Digite seu e-mail e descubra o resultado",
        "placeholder": "Seu endereço de e-mail",
        "send": "ENVIAR",
        "consent1": {
          "text": [
            "Após ler e entender a política de privacidade",
            "eu consinto (marcando a caixa apropriada) o processamento de dados",
            "para os fins indicados no ponto 2, letra A da informação (resumo: responder à solicitação)"
          ]
        },
        "consent2": {
          "text": [
            "Eu consinto (marcando a caixa apropriada) o processamento de dados",
            "para os fins indicados no ponto 2, letra A da informação",
            "(resumo: receber comunicações publicitárias/informativas)"
          ]
        },
        "options": {
          "accept": "Eu consinto",
          "not_accept": "Não consinto"
        }
      },
      {
        "code": "STEP_8",
        "question": "Obrigado!",
        "type": "FINAL",
        "last": "VOCÊ TERMINOU!",
        "email_check": {
          "text": [
            "Verifique sua",
            "caixa de entrada"
          ]
        },
        "store_locator": "VISITE NOSSO LOCALIZADOR DE LOJAS"
      }
    ],
    "de": [
      {
        "code": "SKIN_UNDERTONE",
        "question": "Was ist Ihr Hautunterton?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "ROSA - BEIGE - OLIV",
            "logo": "Pelle_Beige_q1.svg",
            "value": "KÜHL"
          },
          {
            "answer": "PFIRSICH - BERNSTEIN - ELFENBEIN",
            "logo": "Pelle_Pesca_q1.svg",
            "value": "WARM"
          }
        ],
        "next": "WEITER",
        "previous": "ZURÜCK"
      },
      {
        "code": "LIP_COLOR",
        "question": "Welche Farbe haben Ihre Lippen?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "ROSIG",
            "logo": "Labbra_Rosate_q2.webp",
            "value": "KÜHL"
          },
          {
            "answer": "PFIRSICH",
            "logo": "Labbra_Pesca_q2.webp",
            "value": "WARM"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "TANNED_SKIN",
        "question": "Welche Farbe hat Ihre Haut nach dem Bräunen?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "NEIGT ZUM RÖTEN",
            "logo": "Pelle_Arrossata_q3.webp",
            "value": "KÜHL"
          },
          {
            "answer": "GOLDEN",
            "logo": "Pelle_Dorata_q3.webp",
            "value": "WARM"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "NATURAL_HAIR_COLOR",
        "question": "Welche ist Ihre natürliche Haarfarbe?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE_HORIZONTAL",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "DUNKEL (Stufen 1 bis 5)",
            "logo": "Hair_L5_q4.webp",
            "value": "DUNKEL"
          },
          {
            "answer": "MITTEL (Stufen 6 bis 7)",
            "logo": "Hair_L7_q4.webp",
            "value": "MITTEL"
          },
          {
            "answer": "HELL (Stufen 8 bis 11)",
            "logo": "Hair_L9_q4.webp",
            "value": "HELL"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "EYEBROW_COLOR",
        "question": "Welche Farbe haben Ihre Augenbrauen?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE_HORIZONTAL",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "DUNKEL (Stufen 1 bis 5)",
            "logo": "Hair_L5_q4.webp",
            "value": "DUNKEL"
          },
          {
            "answer": "MITTEL (Stufen 6 bis 7)",
            "logo": "Hair_L7_q4.webp",
            "value": "MITTEL"
          },
          {
            "answer": "HELL (Stufen 8 bis 11)",
            "logo": "Hair_L9_q4.webp",
            "value": "HELL"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "PERSONALITY",
        "question": [
          "Wie ist Ihre",
          "Persönlichkeit?"
        ],
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE_VERTICAL",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "SCHÜCHTERN, ZURÜCKHALTEND",
            "logo": "",
            "value": "INTROVERTIERT"
          },
          {
            "answer": "LEBHAFT, AUFGESCHLOSSEN",
            "logo": "",
            "value": "EXTROVERTIERT"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "STEP_7",
        "question": "Sie sind fast fertig",
        "type": "FORM_CONTACT",
        "last": "NUR NOCH EIN SCHRITT",
        "message": "Geben Sie Ihre E-Mail-Adresse ein, um das Ergebnis zu erfahren",
        "placeholder": "Ihre E-Mail-Adresse",
        "send": "SENDEN",
        "consent1": {
          "text": [
            "Nach dem Lesen und Verstehen der Datenschutzrichtlinie",
            "stimme ich der Verarbeitung meiner Daten zu",
            "für die unter Punkt 2 Buchstabe A der Information genannten Zwecke (Zusammenfassung: Beantwortung der Anfrage)"
          ]
        },
        "consent2": {
          "text": [
            "Ich stimme der Verarbeitung meiner Daten zu",
            "für die unter Punkt 2 Buchstabe A der Information genannten Zwecke",
            "(Zusammenfassung: Erhalt von Werbe-/Informationsmitteilungen)"
          ]
        },
        "options": {
          "accept": "Ich stimme zu",
          "not_accept": "Ich stimme nicht zu"
        }
      },
      {
        "code": "STEP_8",
        "question": "Danke!",
        "type": "FINAL",
        "last": "SIE SIND FERTIG!",
        "email_check": {
          "text": [
            "Überprüfen Sie Ihren",
            "E-Mail-Posteingang"
          ]
        },
        "store_locator": "BESUCHEN SIE UNSEREN STORE LOCATOR"
      }
    ],
    "nl": [
      {
        "code": "SKIN_UNDERTONE",
        "question": "Wat is jouw huidondertoon?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "ROZE - BEIGE - OLIVE",
            "logo": "Pelle_Beige_q1.svg",
            "value": "KOEL"
          },
          {
            "answer": "PERZIK - AMBER - IVOOR",
            "logo": "Pelle_Pesca_q1.svg",
            "value": "WARM"
          }
        ],
        "next": "DOORGAAN",
        "previous": "TERUG"
      },
      {
        "code": "LIP_COLOR",
        "question": "Wat is de kleur van jouw lippen?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "ROZIG",
            "logo": "Labbra_Rosate_q2.webp",
            "value": "KOEL"
          },
          {
            "answer": "PERZIK",
            "logo": "Labbra_Pesca_q2.webp",
            "value": "WARM"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "TANNED_SKIN",
        "question": "Welke kleur heeft jouw huid na het zonnen?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "NEIGT NAAR RODE KLEUR",
            "logo": "Pelle_Arrossata_q3.webp",
            "value": "KOEL"
          },
          {
            "answer": "GOUDKLEURIG",
            "logo": "Pelle_Dorata_q3.webp",
            "value": "WARM"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "NATURAL_HAIR_COLOR",
        "question": "Wat is jouw natuurlijke haarkleur?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE_HORIZONTAL",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "DONKER (niveaus 1 tot 5)",
            "logo": "Hair_L5_q4.webp",
            "value": "DONKER"
          },
          {
            "answer": "MIDDEL (niveaus 6 tot 7)",
            "logo": "Hair_L7_q4.webp",
            "value": "MIDDEL"
          },
          {
            "answer": "LICHT (niveaus 8 tot 11)",
            "logo": "Hair_L9_q4.webp",
            "value": "LICHT"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "EYEBROW_COLOR",
        "question": "Wat is de kleur van jouw wenkbrauwen?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE_HORIZONTAL",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "DONKER (niveaus 1 tot 5)",
            "logo": "Hair_L5_q4.webp",
            "value": "DONKER"
          },
          {
            "answer": "MIDDEL (niveaus 6 tot 7)",
            "logo": "Hair_L7_q4.webp",
            "value": "MIDDEL"
          },
          {
            "answer": "LICHT (niveaus 8 tot 11)",
            "logo": "Hair_L9_q4.webp",
            "value": "LICHT"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "PERSONALITY",
        "question": [
          "Hoe is jouw",
          "persoonlijkheid?"
        ],
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE_VERTICAL",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "VERLEGEN, TERUGGETROKKEN",
            "logo": "",
            "value": "INTROVERT"
          },
          {
            "answer": "UITBUNDIG, SPONTAAN",
            "logo": "",
            "value": "EXTRAVERT"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "STEP_7",
        "question": "Je bent bijna klaar",
        "type": "FORM_CONTACT",
        "last": "NOG ÉÉN STAP",
        "message": "Vul je e-mailadres in en ontdek het resultaat",
        "placeholder": "Jouw e-mailadres",
        "send": "VERSTUREN",
        "consent1": {
          "text": [
            "Na het lezen en begrijpen van het privacybeleid",
            "stem ik ermee in (door het juiste vakje aan te vinken) dat mijn gegevens worden verwerkt",
            "voor de doeleinden vermeld in punt 2, letter A van de informatie (samenvatting: beantwoorden van de aanvraag)"
          ]
        },
        "consent2": {
          "text": [
            "Ik stem ermee in (door het juiste vakje aan te vinken) dat mijn gegevens worden verwerkt",
            "voor de doeleinden vermeld in punt 2, letter A van de informatie",
            "(samenvatting: ontvangst van reclame-/informatieberichten)"
          ]
        },
        "options": {
          "accept": "Ik ga akkoord",
          "not_accept": "Ik ga niet akkoord"
        }
      },
      {
        "code": "STEP_8",
        "question": "Bedankt!",
        "type": "FINAL",
        "last": "JE BENT KLAAR!",
        "email_check": {
          "text": [
            "Controleer je",
            "e-mail inbox"
          ]
        },
        "store_locator": "BEZOEK ONZE WINKELLOCATOR"
      }
    ],
    "pl": [
      {
        "code": "SKIN_UNDERTONE",
        "question": "Jaki jest twój odcień skóry?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "RÓŻOWY - BEŻOWY-  OLIVKOWY",
            "logo": "Pelle_Beige_q1.svg",
            "value": "CHŁODNY"
          },
          {
            "answer": "BRZOSKWINIOWY - BURSZTYNOWY KOŚĆ - SŁONIOWA",
            "logo": "Pelle_Pesca_q1.svg",
            "value": "CIEPŁY"
          }
        ],
        "next": "DALEJ",
        "previous": "WRÓĆ"
      },
      {
        "code": "LIP_COLOR",
        "question": "Jaki jest kolor twoich ust?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "RÓŻOWY",
            "logo": "Labbra_Rosate_q2.webp",
            "value": "CHŁODNY"
          },
          {
            "answer": "BRZOSKWINIOWY",
            "logo": "Labbra_Pesca_q2.webp",
            "value": "CIEPŁY"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "TANNED_SKIN",
        "question": "Jaki kolor ma twoja skóra po opalaniu?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "MA TENDENCJĘ DO CZERWIENIENIA SIĘ",
            "logo": "Pelle_Arrossata_q3.webp",
            "value": "CHŁODNY"
          },
          {
            "answer": "ZŁOTY",
            "logo": "Pelle_Dorata_q3.webp",
            "value": "CIEPŁY"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "NATURAL_HAIR_COLOR",
        "question": "Jaki jest twój naturalny kolor włosów?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE_HORIZONTAL",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "CIEMNY (poziomy 1 do 5)",
            "logo": "Hair_L5_q4.webp",
            "value": "CIEMNY"
          },
          {
            "answer": "ŚREDNI (poziomy 6 do 7)",
            "logo": "Hair_L7_q4.webp",
            "value": "ŚREDNI"
          },
          {
            "answer": "JASNY (poziomy 8 do 11)",
            "logo": "Hair_L9_q4.webp",
            "value": "JASNY"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "EYEBROW_COLOR",
        "question": "Jaki jest kolor twoich brwi?",
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE_HORIZONTAL",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "CIEMNY (poziomy 1 do 5)",
            "logo": "Hair_L5_q4.webp",
            "value": "CIEMNY"
          },
          {
            "answer": "ŚREDNI (poziomy 6 do 7)",
            "logo": "Hair_L7_q4.webp",
            "value": "ŚREDNI"
          },
          {
            "answer": "JASNY (poziomy 8 do 11)",
            "logo": "Hair_L9_q4.webp",
            "value": "JASNY"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "PERSONALITY",
        "question": [
          "Jaka jest twoja",
          "osobowość?"
        ],
        "type": "GRID_IMAGE_VERTICAL",
        "replies": [
          {
            "answer": "NIEŚMIAŁA, POWŚCIĄGLIWA",
            "logo": "",
            "value": "INTROWERTYK"
          },
          {
            "answer": "EKSPRESYJNA, TOWARZYSKA",
            "logo": "",
            "value": "EKSTRAWERTYK"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "code": "STEP_7",
        "question": "Jesteś prawie gotowy",
        "type": "FORM_CONTACT",
        "last": "JESZCZE JEDEN KROK",
        "message": "Wpisz swój adres e-mail i odkryj wynik",
        "placeholder": "Twój adres e-mail",
        "send": "WYŚLIJ",
        "consent1": {
          "text": [
            "Po przeczytaniu i zrozumieniu polityki prywatności",
            "wyrażam zgodę (zaznaczając odpowiednie pole) na przetwarzanie moich danych",
            "w celach określonych w punkcie 2 litera A informacji (podsumowanie: odpowiedź na zapytanie)"
          ]
        },
        "consent2": {
          "text": [
            "Wyrażam zgodę (zaznaczając odpowiednie pole) na przetwarzanie moich danych",
            "w celach określonych w punkcie 2 litera A informacji",
            "(podsumowanie: otrzymywanie komunikatów reklamowych/informacyjnych)"
          ]
        },
        "options": {
          "accept": "Zgadzam się",
          "not_accept": "Nie zgadzam się"
        }
      },
      {
        "code": "STEP_8",
        "question": "Dziękujemy!",
        "type": "FINAL",
        "last": "WSZYSTKO GOTOWE!",
        "email_check": {
          "text": [
            "Sprawdź swoją",
            "skrzynkę e-mailową"
          ]
        },
        "store_locator": "ODWIEDŹ NASZĄ LOKALIZACJĘ SKLEPÓW"
      }
    ]
  },
  "result": {
    "it": [
      {
        "title": "ECCO IL TUO RISULTATO",
        "subtitle": "secondo la nostra analisi le famiglie colore per te sono:",
        "text": [
          "puoi abbinare al risultato queste famiglie colore:"
        ],
        "match": "ABBINABILI CON",
        "text_final": [
          "Trova il salone più vicino a te e",
          "chiedigli di Giulietta"
        ],
        "store_locator": "STORE LOCATOR",
        "share_social": "CONDIVIDI SUI SOCIAL"
      }
    ],
    "en": [
      {
        "title": "HERE IS YOUR RESULT",
        "subtitle": "according to our analysis the color families for you are:",
        "text": [
          "you can match these color families with the result:"
        ],
        "match": "MATCHABLE WITH",
        "text_final": [
          "Find the nearest salon to you and",
          "ask them about Giulietta"
        ],
        "store_locator": "STORE LOCATOR",
        "share_social": "SHARE ON SOCIAL MEDIA"
      }
    ],
    "es": [
      {
        "title": "ESTE ES TU RESULTADO",
        "subtitle": "según nuestro análisis, las familias de colores para ti son:",
        "text": [
          "puedes combinar con el resultado estas familias de colores:"
        ],
        "match": "COMBINABLE CON",
        "text_final": [
          "Encuentra el salón más cercano a ti y",
          "pídele a Giulietta"
        ],
        "store_locator": "LOCALIZADOR DE TIENDAS",
        "share_social": "COMPARTE EN LAS REDES SOCIALES"
      }
    ],
    "fr": [
      {
        "title": "VOICI VOTRE RÉSULTAT",
        "subtitle": "selon notre analyse, les familles de couleurs pour vous sont :",
        "text": [
          "vous pouvez associer à ce résultat ces familles de couleurs :"
        ],
        "match": "ASSOCIABLE AVEC",
        "text_final": [
          "Trouvez le salon le plus proche de chez vous et",
          "demandez à Giulietta"
        ],
        "store_locator": "LOCALISATEUR DE MAGASINS",
        "share_social": "PARTAGEZ SUR LES RÉSEAUX SOCIAUX"
      }
    ],
    "pt": [
      {
        "title": "ESSE É O SEU RESULTADO",
        "subtitle": "segundo nossa análise, as famílias de cores para você são:",
        "text": [
          "você pode combinar com o resultado essas famílias de cores:"
        ],
        "match": "COMBINÁVEL COM",
        "text_final": [
          "Encontre o salão mais próximo de você e",
          "peça para Giulietta"
        ],
        "store_locator": "LOCALIZADOR DE LOJAS",
        "share_social": "COMPARTILHE NAS REDES SOCIAIS"
      }
    ],
    "de": [
      {
        "title": "DAS IST DEIN ERGEBNIS",
        "subtitle": "laut unserer Analyse sind die Farbfamilien für dich:",
        "text": [
          "du kannst mit diesem Ergebnis diese Farbfamilien kombinieren:"
        ],
        "match": "KOMBINIERT MIT",
        "text_final": [
          "Finde den nächsten Salon und",
          "frage nach Giulietta"
        ],
        "store_locator": "STANDORTFINDER",
        "share_social": "TEILE IN DEN SOZIALEN NETZWERKEN"
      }
    ],
    "nl": [
      {
        "title": "DIT IS JE RESULTAAT",
        "subtitle": "volgens onze analyse zijn de kleurfamilies voor jou:",
        "text": [
          "je kunt met dit resultaat de volgende kleurfamilies combineren:"
        ],
        "match": "COMBINEREN MET",
        "text_final": [
          "Vind de dichtstbijzijnde salon en",
          "vraag naar Giulietta"
        ],
        "store_locator": "WINKELVINDER",
        "share_social": "DEEL OP SOCIAL MEDIA"
      }
    ],
    "pl": [
      {
        "title": "TO JEST TWOJ WYNIK",
        "subtitle": "zgodnie z naszą analizą, rodziny kolorów dla Ciebie to:",
        "text": [
          "możesz dopasować do tego wyniku następujące rodziny kolorów:"
        ],
        "match": "MOŻLIWE DO POŁĄCZENIA Z",
        "text_final": [
          "Znajdź najbliższy salon i",
          "zapytaj o Giuliettę"
        ],
        "store_locator": "LOKALIZATOR SKLEPÓW",
        "share_social": "UDOSTĘPNIJ W SOCIAL MEDIACH"
      }
    ]
  },
  "footer": {
    "it": {
      "text": [
        "Pettenon Cosmetics S.p.A. S.B. sede legale in via del Palù, 7/D, 35018 - San Martino di Lupari (PD - Italia)",
        "Cod. Fisc., P.Iva e Registro delle Imprese di Padova n. 04937500280, R.E.A. PD 430007",
        "Cap. Soc. €7.500.000,00 i.v., società soggetta a direzione e coordinamento di AGF88 Holding S.r.l."
      ],
      "privacy_policy": "Privacy Policy",
      "cookie_policy": "Cookie Policy",
      "terms_of_use": "Termini d'uso"
    },
    "en": {
      "text": [
        "Pettenon Cosmetics S.p.A. S.B. sede legale in via del Palù, 7/D, 35018 - San Martino di Lupari (PD - Italia)",
        "Cod. Fisc., P.Iva e Registro delle Imprese di Padova n. 04937500280, R.E.A. PD 430007",
        "Cap. Soc. €7.500.000,00 i.v., società soggetta a direzione e coordinamento di AGF88 Holding S.r.l."
      ],
      "privacy_policy": "Privacy Policy",
      "cookie_policy": "Cookie Policy",
      "terms_of_use": "Terms of Use"
    },
    "es": {
      "text": [
        "Pettenon Cosmetics S.p.A. S.B. sede legale in via del Palù, 7/D, 35018 - San Martino di Lupari (PD - Italia)",
        "Cod. Fisc., P.Iva e Registro delle Imprese di Padova n. 04937500280, R.E.A. PD 430007",
        "Cap. Soc. €7.500.000,00 i.v., società soggetta a direzione e coordinamento di AGF88 Holding S.r.l."
      ],
      "privacy_policy": "Política de privacidad",
      "cookie_policy": "Política de cookies",
      "terms_of_use": "Términos de uso"
    },
    "fr": {
      "text": [
        "Pettenon Cosmetics S.p.A. S.B. sede legale in via del Palù, 7/D, 35018 - San Martino di Lupari (PD - Italia)",
        "Cod. Fisc., P.Iva e Registro delle Imprese di Padova n. 04937500280, R.E.A. PD 430007",
        "Cap. Soc. €7.500.000,00 i.v., società soggetta a direzione e coordinamento di AGF88 Holding S.r.l."
      ],
      "privacy_policy": "Politique de confidentialité",
      "cookie_policy": "Politique de cookies",
      "terms_of_use": "Conditions d'utilisation"
    },
    "pt": {
      "text": [
        "Pettenon Cosmetics S.p.A. S.B. sede legale in via del Palù, 7/D, 35018 - San Martino di Lupari (PD - Italia)",
        "Cod. Fisc., P.Iva e Registro delle Imprese di Padova n. 04937500280, R.E.A. PD 430007",
        "Cap. Soc. €7.500.000,00 i.v., società soggetta a direzione e coordinamento di AGF88 Holding S.r.l."
      ],
      "privacy_policy": "Política de Privacidade",
      "cookie_policy": "Política de Cookies",
      "terms_of_use": "Termos de uso"
    },
    "de": {
      "text": [
        "Pettenon Cosmetics S.p.A. S.B. sede legale in via del Palù, 7/D, 35018 - San Martino di Lupari (PD - Italia)",
        "Cod. Fisc., P.Iva e Registro delle Imprese di Padova n. 04937500280, R.E.A. PD 430007",
        "Cap. Soc. €7.500.000,00 i.v., società soggetta a direzione e coordinamento di AGF88 Holding S.r.l."
      ],
      "privacy_policy": "Datenschutzerklärung",
      "cookie_policy": "Cookie-Richtlinie",
      "terms_of_use": "Nutzungsbedingungen"
    },
    "nl": {
      "text": [
        "Pettenon Cosmetics S.p.A. S.B. sede legale in via del Palù, 7/D, 35018 - San Martino di Lupari (PD - Italia)",
        "Cod. Fisc., P.Iva e Registro delle Imprese di Padova n. 04937500280, R.E.A. PD 430007",
        "Cap. Soc. €7.500.000,00 i.v., società soggetta a direzione e coordinamento di AGF88 Holding S.r.l."
      ],
      "privacy_policy": "Privacybeleid",
      "cookie_policy": "Cookiebeleid",
      "terms_of_use": "Gebruiksvoorwaarden"
    },
    "pl": {
      "text": [
        "Pettenon Cosmetics S.p.A. S.B. sede legale in via del Palù, 7/D, 35018 - San Martino di Lupari (PD - Italia)",
        "Cod. Fisc., P.Iva e Registro delle Imprese di Padova n. 04937500280, R.E.A. PD 430007",
        "Cap. Soc. €7.500.000,00 i.v., società soggetta a direzione e coordinamento di AGF88 Holding S.r.l."
      ],
      "privacy_policy": "Polityka prywatności",
      "cookie_policy": "Polityka plików cookie",
      "terms_of_use": "Warunki użytkowania"
    }
  }
}